Hoskins, James Whittier, 1799-1833. Sermons, 1820-1833 (bMS 549): A Finding Aid.
Sermons, 1820-1833.
Andover-Harvard Theological Library, Harvard Divinity School
bMS 549
Hoskins, James Whittier, 1799-1833.
1 box
Sermons of Universalist minister James Whittier Hoskins.
James Whittier Hoskins (1799-1833) began preaching in 1822 and was received into fellowship with the Maine Convention of Universalists in 1833. He served parishes in Hampden and Bangor, Maine.
- Sermon entitled Materialism and immaterialism (August 5, 1820)
- Sermon on Gen 1:1 entitled Sheol and Hades (Hampden and Camden, Maine; July 1820)
- Sermon on Gen 18:14
- Sermon on Prov 16:37
- Sermon on Is 26:9
- Sermon on Is 55:7 (Hampden, Maine; April 4, 1832)
- Sermon on Joel 1:14
- Sermon on Matt 4:9
- Sermon on Matt 7:13-14
- Sermon on Matt 15:13
- Sermon on Acts 28:22
- Sermon on Rom 3:31 (Hampden, Maine; January 7, 1833)
- Sermon on 1 Tim 1:15
- Sermon on 2 Tim 1:12
- Sermon on 2 Tim 4:1
- Sermon on Heb 11:1 (Hampden, Maine; April 18, 1833)
- Sermon on Heb 11:6
- Sermon on Heb 12:14 (Hampden, Maine; March 24, 1833)
- Sermon on 1 Pet 1:5-7
- Sermon on 1 Pet 3:18-20
- Sermon on 1 John 3:3
- Sermon on Jude 7
- Sermon on Rev 22:10